Mustafa Furkan Yıldız

Manufacturing Engineer



Contact



+90 532 701 9031



m.furkanyildiz0@gmail.com



Ankara, TURKEY

About Me

He is a manufacturing engineer who has been involved in machining since his university life and has worked on CNC programming, cutting tools and toolroom technologies in his business life. His goal is to keep up with the developing technology and become a well-known machining engineer in the sector.

Certification

- CSWA Mechanical Design (SOLIDWORKS)
- Sales Onboarding (SOLIDWORKS)
- Callobrative Robot
 Programming (FANUC)
- Geometric Tolerances
 (UDEMY)

Education

PostgraduateGazi University

2023 - cont.

Bechalor's Degree
Gazi University

2014 - 2020

Highschool
Suleyman Demirel
Science High School

2014 - 2020

Experience

Service and Application Engineer

HAIMER

07/2023 - cont.

Service, training and applications for HAIMER product to customer.

Customer calls and visits to sell maintenance.

Area Sales Engineer

CNC Ileri Teknoloji

02/2023 - 04/2023

Active customer visit for the sale of HAAS and Makino brand CNC machines.

Product Manager

ABK Teknik

07/2021 - 02/2023

Programming 3, 4 and 5 axis CNC machines and 6, 8 axis industrial robots. Training of CAMWorks and SprutCAM products to customers. Editing post processors for 3, 4, 5 axis CNC mahines.

Sales Engineer

TRS Makina

01/2020 - 06/2020

Determining tool and machining parameters according to material and geometry. Choosing right cutting tool and improve the production of companies.

References

Fürgan MİHMAT

Ulvi ŞEKER

Ankatool / Founder

Gazi University / Faculty Member